<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><Knowledge>   <KnowledgeTagName>VIZNET REPROCESS</KnowledgeTagName>   <KnowledgeTagDesc>If the source is VIZNET then we need to do the VIZNET reprocessselect * from wqms.wqms_order_details where wqms_id='''Take the backup and note the Order id and order completion date and sr no Order doc type should be commissionedEnter the sr no in below querydelete from wqms.wqms_order_details where SR_NO=''Open WIN SCPEnter the details are as given belowServer1: 172.16.34.85Server2: 172.16.34.86Port number: 5522User id: esb8userPassword: E@u@q1vfsPath:root/IBM/apps/wqms/Viznet/FTPArchiveDir LoginSearch all commissioned files for next date of order completion date and copy that fileopen new spread sheet in OPEN OFFICECopy that all commissioned files in that sheetSearch for that perticular order id and select that row delete rest of all the rowsSave that file as ALL_COMMISSIONED_CIRCUITS.csvAgain in winscp select eventdirIn eventdir copy that all commissioned file and refresh then once this file is added then check in order details table by that order id, there we can find new wqms id.</KnowledgeTagDesc>   <KnowledgeTagName>User not mapped issue</KnowledgeTagName>   <KnowledgeTagDesc>For this case we need to check wqms id in process admin.There will be an error.We have to click on that error.Then in right side there will be one opinion like retry failed steps.Click on that and click on ok.Then user name will be visible.</KnowledgeTagDesc>   <KnowledgeTagName>Access required for DMS bulk upload</KnowledgeTagName>   <KnowledgeTagDesc>To privide the access for DMS bulk uploadwe need to check in process admin-server admin-group managementSelect WQMS-DMS-userIn that if that perticular user name is not there means we have to click on add members, in that select that perticular user name and click on add selected.</KnowledgeTagDesc>   <KnowledgeTagName>Data updation</KnowledgeTagName>   <KnowledgeTagDesc>For any data updation first we need to check in database.If it is null we can update.For any data change we need to take approval and SDP ticket details.Once we get all these details then only we have to update.</KnowledgeTagDesc>   <KnowledgeTagName>ESB server restart</KnowledgeTagName>   <KnowledgeTagDesc>ESB url--https://172.16.34.85:9043/ibm/console/login.do?action=secure</KnowledgeTagDesc>   <KnowledgeTagName>ESB server restart</KnowledgeTagName>   <KnowledgeTagDesc>ESB url--https://172.16.34.85:9043/ibm/console/login.do?action=secure</KnowledgeTagDesc>   <KnowledgeTagName>Procedure of the automated account mapping</KnowledgeTagName><KnowledgeTagDesc>Procedure to map the account number:-Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceStep-1    Check whether the given account are already mapped with the given WQMS ID or not in wqms_order_details and wqms_account_details table, if already mapped inform the user.Step-2     If not mapped, update it in Edit plus.Step -3   Enter the WQMS_ID and the account number. Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceStep -4   Concatenate it by using keyword (Ctrl+H).Double click on the space between the wqms_id and the account number. Place comma (,) and click on replace and close the dialog box.Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceStep -5   Open the command prompt (cmd.exe).Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-Space               Type cd desktopNon-Break-SpaceNon-Break-Space                cd  "Account Mapping"Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-Space                dirNon-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceThe following path appears on the screen Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-Space              C:\Users\Mastercom\Desktop\Account mapping&gt;Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceNon-Break-SpaceEnter the wqms account number map bat (press tab key) and the file name as shown below. Non-Break-SpaceNon-Break-Space Wqms_acc_map.bat  Test.csv</KnowledgeTagDesc></Knowledge>